{
    "id": "0aae43b0a0754460a8ae11b40b206d5f",
    "title": "Inseparable phrasal verbs exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "d8ad79f7d0334cf6ba341faedcfc849e",
            "title": "Inseparable Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "He continues to call …………………….. his old colleagues.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "in",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "It took me quite some time to get………………………. my breakup with Nancy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "on",
                        "over",
                        "off"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I need to go ……………………. the documents again before I can arrive at a decision.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "out",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has already gone ……………………. all his money.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "through",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jane has agreed to look ………………… my baby when I am gone.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "after",
                        "at",
                        "for"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The officer said that he would look ………………………. the matter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "at",
                        "after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ran ……………………. an old friend of mine yesterday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "across",
                        "at",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ran …………………… Mary at the super market.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "into",
                        "after",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I look forward …………………….. hearing from you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to",
                        "for",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I couldn’t believe my eyes when I saw my old boss waiting ……………………. tables.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "at",
                        "on",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}